Correct.
Only one load and if the particular order
goes a change, undergoes a change,
we have a way to handle those.
But my question was,
there is no way in I can I can I can do
this in order to change, right?
We are just for changing.
No, not in an order change in a PGI,
you can do it.
Okay, I see this.
Mm.
Okay.
So, let me, let me bring back my question.
Yeah.
And let's go to the to the personal.
We got to order exchange here.
Let's go with the console.
He's still gone.
Good.
So it says here consolidated or changed.
So it says when a planner saves with
orders still in pending.
Like, what happens to those orders?
What do you mean by pending?
And the status of the,
I think it was the status of the
shipments, the order.
I don't know, is that a pending status?
I'm not clear of that.
There is, oh, okay, there is no, yeah,
because only the created orders are,
because I think it's here,
the order status is referring to this.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, but there is I don't see pending.
There is no pending, right?
It's just ready for planning, hold,
planning failed, and so on.
Yeah, yeah.
Done.
After approve changes, what's the flow?
Oh, rerouting, reroute.
Yeah.
The IDAD,
once the order is created and there is an
update that comes in,
immediately those updates are applied.
There is no approval to that update.
Okay, so they are applied.
directly applied on the order and those
changes are cascaded to the shipment,
And then...
right? That means it comes on to the load,
load gets updated or the order is mapped
inside a shipment,
the shipment is also updated.
So when that shipment is updated and if
it is already tendered,
you know the scenario how it happens.
Yeah, all of those.
So everything happens again, right?
Correct,
everything now it is needs to be put to
the user for review,
because the system cannot make a decision
because a tender has been sent for a
certain configuration,
and now that configuration has changed
because of an order change,
one of the order in a consolidation,
one of the order in the console.
had a change and because of that,
there was a change and the system could
not decide. So in that case,
what it is going to do is it is going to
mark that particular shipment as order
change for that user.
Okay.
No, yeah, not that user,
but generally for users to review and
take an action.
Um...
Of changes. OK, that that is close.
Let's go to the third one.
So...
I'm gonna call a reprocess that, okay?
And.
Third one,
can orders whose shipment already has a
tender since be added?
An order whose shipment already has a
tender sent be added. Added means.
Yeah, I don't think this is because added,
I think that it means this part.
Let's go to a consolidated one.
We are waiting.
is receding, the database is receding.
But do you remember the place where we
had...
Where we used to have.
We can search and add order.
That's when you're saying.
Exactly, exactly. Got it.
Yeah, yeah, you can. For order change,
you can review, add a new order,
do a simulation,
check all those things as possible.
So if when you are adding an order,
then you are basically consolidating,
right?
Yeah, I can also move.
It could be a consolidated shipment.
Smile.
I could move an order from a different
shipment, which is also a consolidation.
OK.
Not necessary that I am trying to move an
order and just wanted to make it into a
consolidation.
Already it is a consolidation.
If it's a direct shipment,
I'm trying to move it,
it's definitely going to turn into
consolidation.
Okay,
because when I'm searching that order
that I want to add,
that is the full list of all of the
orders that exist, right?
And what happens if that order is in a
shipment that is being sent? All right,
then they're sent. Is that possible?
Yeah,
then it would say that it would say that
you cannot add the order into the,
you can do the what of scenario,
you cannot finalize it, right?
It would it would tell when you were
Ohh.
about to go and finalize,
it'll say that you need to cancel the
tender and then move the order.
OK.
And then...
But when that rules applies,
when it's sent, when it's accepted,
where else? A cancel?
I think it is in the story, right?
I could not remember all the rules.
Tender sent, accepted, and to be tendered.
Begin there.
The tender, okay,
when I consolidate shipment,
the tender tab review already changed,
button jumps to the stop stack.
I cannot confirm this.
Let's go with the next one.
The 2 foundation stories are on hold
waiting for the on the optimized issue.
So, I just ignored his sense.
Because they say that they are on hold
waiting for the optimization.
If you can check that story that I added,
right,
so it has solved that particular thing.
Save processing, uh, subsequent shipment,
adding validation stuff, analyzation,
frequent sequencing, pickup gate,
delivery date, existing stuff.
Second, not that one, yeah,
select order from.
Ah, this story, right?
I'll give you the lens.
15870.
Yeah.
Oh, it's actually...
1543 5
In 1543, 6.
1543 5 is 1543 5 and 6. Yeah,
those are first stories of the
consolidation, consolidated order change.
It says on hold. I don't remember.
Could you check?
Because here it says it what they were at
fault waiting for the optimizer.
What do you mean? Two foundation stories,
15 or on hold, waiting for optimizer.
You mean?
Or maybe the team marked it for hold,
something like that.
I mean...
Okay, I will just ignore that.
Yeah.
Yeah, you just ignore that.
There is a status that the team marked it
to say that it is on hold,
but I don't think so.
Why did they move it?
Sony Optimizer integration depends on it.
It is on hold as discussed with Soni by
Deepesh. So he did it like Mayank.
I'll just ignore it for now.
Yeah.
Yeah, OK. I think hopefully this is.
Landing soon. Sorry, Jenna.
It's because whenever I have to make sure
the one of the fields need to match what
we have in the stops for in any tab,
I need to reset the entire database.
You know, that is why I'm not there.
I mean, it takes a couple of minutes, but.
..
Okay.
Let's go then with your,
with the next thing that you want to talk
about, with the things that are missing.
Okay, yeah.
Then we can go to the person.
Sorry, Manuela, instead of sharing,
I clicked on leave.
It happened to me multiple times as well.
Just give me a second.
OK, let me share my screen.
Okay, we are clear about this one,
so you might have to change to get the
prior, and then we will have new. Okay,
once the changes have been made, right,
What machine?
once the changes have been made from
question mark,
it has been rearranged and you have a
sequence, right, top P1, P2, P3, and P4,
right?
The user can click on the view routing
and see the routing information, right?
Save, OK,
click on this and see the routing
information.
Once again, once again, let me see.
What is the first step? Is it like?
No, okay, I think you need to do this one.
Save first.
Alright, so once you do this,
you click on the save action.
Once you click, click on the save action,
there are two things.
Ah, okay, let me do this one first.
So once it is reorganized and the view
routing button is eliminated, right?
So once it is finalized and all done,
the view routing button is there.
The user clicks on the view routing
Okay.
button,
they will be able to see the tender
information, right?
So that is what it says.
The distance are updated after.
The user clicks on view routing,
and also user will get to see the carrier
list, so they will be able to,
once they did all this,
they will say that, okay,
they will click on view routing, right?
So, once they click on the view routing,
then the distance are all updated because
it's going to call the routing service,
gets the distance,
and all that it is going to.
calculate and then it is going to
populate the user with the route
information, right?
The route rank and all those details.
This makes sense so far.
Yes.
Okay,
so if the user is satisfied with this
particular thing,
what they will do is they will go and do
the save action.
In the Save action,
there are two possibilities that can
happen.
User can click Save to finalize the
change.
Once the user finalizes the change,
then two possibilities are there.
There is an existing tender that was sent
out even before this change had happened,
right?
There is a current existing tender and
something was sent or accepted by the
carrier, right? You need to address that.
That is 1 possibility.
The second possibility for a
consolidation is the prior tender does
not exist.
This is a consolidation that was recently
built by the user,
but suddenly an order change came in,
right? If that order change came in,
still the user will have to address it,
unlike the direct shipment order change,
right? The user will have to address this,
and it follows a different workflow.
So there are two workflows that...
happens on clicking on save.
Makes sense.
Yes, that is 1. Well, it's still updated.
Right.
Okay,
I'll go through each of those workflow,
right? But I'm just telling you,
save can lead to two options based on the
condition,
the current condition of the shipment.
If the shipment is already tendered to a
carrier and accepted,
then it will follow the route A process.
The prior tender was accepted to a
carrier or sent to a carrier,
it will follow prior.
Step A process.
If there was no prior tender,
but the order change came in for a
consolidated shipment,
it will follow the step B process.
Okay, and the third option is cancel.
The user can cancel,
Yeah.
forget about all the changes they made,
they can exit and go back to this one,
right, the prior, and leave it as it is.
They can make a decision.
That's one possibility.
Okay.
Right now,
if the user goes with the first option,
right,
there was a there is a prior tender and
the prior tender is sent or accepted by a
carrier and there is a new routing list
that is available with the new set of
carriers, then how they will do it,
and that is where.
We get to the same old screen as we do it
for.
Direct shipment.
Right,
if there is a prior tender that is
already available for this particular
console, right,
it will list these options: cancel tender,
re-tender, bypass tender,
and the logic remains the same,
whether the user will want to keep the
prior cost, want to add a new cost,
or a new quote, right?
And what is the prior value?
What is the new value? New shipment,
right? Say for example,
this new tender list is there and the
prior tender list is there.
In the prior, it is sent. In the new,
the same carrier, ODFL. ODFL is not there,
right?
So if the user prefers to have that same
carrier added,
they could choose the prior cost and add
this carrier as rank #3 inside the new
tender list.
Right,
and they can either re-tender or bypass
tender.
Because this carrier is not part of the
list,
Okay.
there is no pickup date and delivery date.
Make sense?
The pickup date and delivery date comes
from, for the consolidated shipment,
it comes from the stops.
The pickup date is the first pickup date
of the stop,
and the delivery date is the last
delivery date of the stop.
Make sense?
because it's a consolidation.
Routing cannot decide on a consolidated
shipment when it will be its pickup date
and delivery date.
That date will come from this one.
the pickup date here and the delivery
date here. In A consolidation,
that is the rule.
It has to forget the routing guides,
pickup date and delivery date.
It has to go with the user selected
pickup date and delivery date.
Yes, of course,
because you are planning on that.
Correct, exactly, because it...
I have a question, Janardhana.
Uh-huh.
I am not,
I don't have a clear understanding on how
the routing list appears, right?
So whenever we are tendering something.
There is a list of carriers, right?
What is the logic, right? Like,
it's about ranking, right?
But how do I know how many carriers I can
list? Some of them.
You, you, yeah,
there is an engine that is a there is a
routing engine which decides on the
equipment asked on the order, right?
Back.
Order gets converted onto a load,
so load has its orders equipment,
it has the...
pickup date, delivery date,
and there is an equipment.
The equipment is given and there are a
few other information which is sent to
that engine.
The engine looks into that those
parameters and then looks into who are
the carriers operating for that pickup
and or pickup destination and the
delivery destination and loads those
carriers in a list.
Ohh, OK, so this this process,
this engine process happens once I do an
order change, right?
A consolidated order change, so...
Yeah, whenever, whenever you save,
whenever you click on save,
Wherever I say.
it goes and calls the routing service.
Okay.
OK, makes sense. This one,
then it follows the same process as that
of the direct shipment, right? So,
because it has a...
Yeah.
Prior tender, since it has a prior tender,
decision on the prior tender needs to be
taken, right?
This is the decision screen for the prior
tender and the new tender.
Whether you go on the new tender with the
same carrier,
even though that carrier is not there,
but if that carrier is listed in this one
but is in a different rank,
do you want to use so?
Old cost or the new cost?
or you want to give a new quote.
All those options do come up the same way
how we did it in direct shipment.
Once the user takes this decision,
the decision is applied onto the tender
itself, right?
So that the new tender will have this
ODFL inserted into the list,
and then it'll have this,
it'll have its own rate.
and rest of the information is filled and
that will be available on the tender
screen with all the changes made.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
So, save is the last action, right?
The last action.
Save is the last action, correct?
I think I put on a different name to that.
I think I put it as a fly or something.
Okay.
I will review it.
Okay.
Okay, save, save, right?
Right.
I mean,
just apply means apply this order change,
this, this planner, but say...
Yeah.
changes associated with they removed an
order, that they kept the order,
whatever it is, and they rearranged it.
Whatever they did here,
they are finalizing it with the same.
Right? Once they finalize,
immediately ask the user what to do with
the existing tender,
if it has an existing tender,
Yeah.
because we are talking about a scenario
where an existing tender,
where prior tender exists or existing
tender is there, right?
How to handle that existing tender.
So that is going to give a decision
screen.
to the user to make a decision on the...
prior tender, right?
Suppose if there is no prior tender,
there is no existing tender to any
carrier.
So it will automatically apply all these
changes and take the user to the tender
screen with this new tender list.
If there is no tender list and has only
drop carriers,
it will show only the drop carriers.
And the user will decide what to do next.
I was thinking about apply instead of
save because save means sometimes what
happens if I did all of these changes in
order to change and then I leave,
I just exit the screen or I don't know,
internet goes down, right?
Maybe I say this setting that I've been
doing right and apply means apply and go
to the routing and rendering.
Just the terminology, whichever is okay,
you can do it. Apply or save.
I'm okay with both.
But you don't have this in functionality,
right? Where you have,
where you are planning something and then
you just close it, that will be reset,
right?
No, no,
I have a specific word called safe.
Then.
So your changes will be saved, right?
Despite not applying. Applying means...
Correct.
Not apply, save.
OK, let's do it.
It means save my changes, right?
Yes, like, save, save your work changes,
right? Your the Word documents.
Yeah, but correct. Whatever I've done,
save it and then immediately triggers the
next workflow because you are saving it
and there is a decision that needs to be
taken by the user.
because there is a prior tender.
If there is no tender,
No.
then this is saved and it exits the
screen and goes to the tender screen.
It will go to the screen.
Okay, yeah, okay.
It will come to the screen.
Directly, and then you can do whatever.
Yeah.
then the user can tender to a particular
carrier or do whatever action they want.
But it won't be an auto tender, right?
Yeah, from stop it will move to tender,
right? They will be in stop.
From stop it will jump. Once they save,
it will jump to tender.
For example,
when you add a carrier right now,
when you manually add a carrier, right,
we are not tendering to that carrier
until you click on the track.
Correct.
Is that the same same logic? Ohh, no,
it's different.
Same logic. Yeah, otherwise, correct.
Same logic.
The same logic because the user is now
left to decide what needs to be done.
OK, fine.
So is that it? I think that's it, right?
That closes the loop. There is something.
Correct, that closes the loop. That's it.
This was the part that was missing, right?
View routing will give them a view of the
routing,
Yeah.
calling the routing once it is like,
you know, they have set,
they can click on no question marks are
there. See, that's what I've written.
User has moved the stops P question mark
to P2. Now the stop is named as P2.
P2 is changed to P3, Atlanta,
whatever the changes they made.
Then once all this is set,
they can click on routing.
They can see the routing before they go
ahead and save it, right?
Yeah.
So that is why we have view routing.
So once they are happy with the routing
list and everything they got,
then they can go and hit on save and then
it pops them this question.
Based on the condition one,
if there are no questions,
it leads to two and directly put them in
the tender screen.
It's playing.
Yeah, this one is a bit complex.
It's not very straightforward.
This.
It has a lot of things to do.
The other one was also very good,
maybe it was new.
Correct, correct.
It's just by looking at it again and
again and again,
your brain gets tuned and you start
understanding it even better. All right.
Thanks.
Okay.
Right now,
I don't think my seat has been done.
Still, the background agent is working.
Have you launched already?
Yeah, I had my lunch, yeah.
Ohh no, okay then.
I have other things to take care.
We can talk later if you want.
Are you got?
Okay,
can we wait a couple of maybe an hour and
we can talk?
Sure, sure, yeah.
Thank you, Janardhana.
Take care. Bye-bye. Talk to you later.
Bye.